Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- DC Comics
  - Contents of Box 111: (Box 111)
    - Title from indicia: Jonah Hex Spectacular, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Legion of Super-Heroes Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Madame Xanadu, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Mask, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Men of War, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Nathaniel Dusk II, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Nathaniel Dusk Private Investigator II
    - Title from indicia: Our Fighting Forces, Issues from: 1970s
      - Cover Title: Our Fighting Forces featuring The Losers
    - Title from indicia: Plastic Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Secrets of the Haunted House Special, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock Special, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock Spectacular, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Stalker, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy Spectacular, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Superman Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Superman Spectacular, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: The Unexpected Special, Issues from: 1970s
    - Title from indicia: V, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 112: (Box 112)
    - Title from indicia: All-American Men of War, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Our Fighting Forces, Issues from: 1950s
  - Contents of Box 113: (Box 113)
    - Title from indicia: Our Army at War, Issues from: 1950s,1960s,1970s
      - Cover Title: Our Army at War, Issues from: 1950s
      - Cover Title: Our Army at War featuring Sgt. Rock, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 114: (Box 114)
    - Title from indicia: Our Army at War, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sensation Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
      - Cover Title: Sensation Comics (Wonder Woman)1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sensation Mystery, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 115: (Box 115)
    - Title from indicia: The Flash, Issues from: 1950s,1960s,1970s
  - Contents of Box 116: (Box 116)
    - Title from indicia: G.I. Combat, Issues from: 1970s,1980s
    - Title from indicia: G.I. War Tales, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 117: (Box 117)
    - Title from indicia: The Adventures of Rex the Wonder Dog, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: All-American Men of War, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Brave and the Bold, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Classics Illustrated, Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: Flash Comics
    - Title from indicia: Flash Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Hopalong Cassidy, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Our Fighting Forces, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Star-Spangled War Stories, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Three Mouseketeers, Issues from: 1950s
  - Contents of Box 118: (Box 118)
    - Title from indicia: Bomba the Jungle Boy, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Capt. Storm, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: P.T. Boat Skipper Capt. Storm
    - Title from indicia: G.I. Combat, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 119: (Box 119)
    - Title from indicia: The Adventures of Alan Ladd, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: All American Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: All American Men of War, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: All American Western, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
    - Title from indicia: Dale Evans Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Frontier Fighters, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: G.I. Combat, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Hopalong Cassidy, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Jimmy Wakely, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: The Legends of Daniel Boone, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Our Fighting Forces, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Sugar and Spike, Issues from: 1960s,1970s
  - Contents of Box 120: (Box 120)
    - Title from indicia: House of Mystery, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: House of Secrets, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Sugar and Spike, Issues from: 1950s
  - Contents of Box 121: (Box 121)
    - Title from indicia: The Adventures of Rex the Wonder Dog, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Anthro, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Atom, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Atom & Hawkman, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Batman Annual, Issues from: 1960s
      Issues 1-5
      - Cover Title: Giant Batman Annual
    - Title from indicia: Beware the Creeper, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Captain Action, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: From Beyond the Unknown, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: The Hawk and the Dove, Issues from: 1960s
    - Title from indicia: Our Army at War, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Rip Hunter... Time Master, Issues from: 1960s
  - Contents of Box 122: (Box 122)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1930s,1940s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Adventure Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
      - Cover Title: Adventures Comics (Superboy)
    - Title from indicia: All American Comics, Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: All American Comics (Green Lantern)
    - Title from indicia: All-Flash, DC/All-American, Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: All-Flash
    - Title from indicia: Flash Comics, DC/All-American Issues from: 1940s
      - Cover Title: Flash Comics>
  - Contents of Box 123: (Box 123)
    - Title from indicia: All-Flash, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: All-Star Comics, DC/All-American, DC/All-American Issues from: 1940s,1950s
      - Cover Title: All-Star Comics
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1950s, 1960s
      Issues 92-129
    - Title from indicia: The Brave and the Bold, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Flash Comics, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern Quarterly, Issues from: 1940s
    - Title from indicia: Mystery in Space, Issues from: 1950s
    - Title from indicia: Strange Adventures, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
    - Title from indicia: Superman's Pal Jimmy Olsen, Issues from: 1950s
  - Contents of Box 124: (Box 124)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1940s,1950s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1960s
      Issues 130-144
    - Title from indicia: Mystery in Space, Issues from: 1950s,1960s
  - Contents of Box 125: (Box 125)
    - Title from indicia: Star Spangled War Stories, Issues from: 1950s,1960s,1970s
      - Cover Title: Star Spangled War Stories, Issues from: 1950s,1960s,1970s
      - Cover Title: Enemy Ace, Issues from: 1960s
      - Cover Title: The Unknown Soldier, Issues from: 1970s
  - Contents of Box 126: (Box 126)
    - Title from indicia: All-Star Squadron, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Centurions, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Crisis on Infinite Earths, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Manhunter, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Martian Manhunter, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Origins, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Secret Origins Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Tailgunner, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of the Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Tales of the Teen Titans, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Talos of the Wilderness Sea, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Teen Titans Spotlight, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Vigilante, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Vigilante Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Warlord, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Warlord Annual, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 127: (Box 127)
    - Title from indicia: Amethyst, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Amethyst Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Angel Love, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Elvira's House of Mystery, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Elvira's House of Mystery Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: G.I. Combat, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Millennium, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Mister Miracle, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Mister Miracle Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Omega Men, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Power Girl, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Power of the Atom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Roots of the Swamp Thing, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sgt. Rock Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Shadow, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Shadow Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Silver Blade, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectre, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectre Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Swamp Thing, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Unknown Soldier, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wasteland, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wrath of the Spectre, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 128: (Box 128)
    - Title from indicia: Blackhawk, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Doc Savage, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Doom Patrol, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Doom Patrol Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Flash, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Flash Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Fury of Firestorm, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Firestorm the Nuclear Man
    - Title from indicia: Fury of Firestorm Annual, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Firestorm Annual
    - Title from indicia: Green Arrow, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Green Arrow Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Green Arrow: The Longbow Hunters, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Green Lantern Corps, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Lords of the Ultra-Realm, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: New Gods, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: New Guardians, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Rainbow Brite and the Star Stealer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Shazam: The New Beginning, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Starman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek Movie Special, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home
    - Title from indicia: Star Trek: The Next Generation, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sword of the Atom Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Who's Who in Star Trek, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 129: (Box 129)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics Weekly, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batgirl Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 1980s
      Issues 391-393, 398-400, 404-406, 410-411, 414, 416-423, 430
    - Title from indicia: Batman Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batman and the Outsiders, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: The Dark Knight Returns, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: The Cult, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: The Killing Joke, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman 1,000,000, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman: Guardian of Gotham, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman/Wildcat, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Cinder and Ashe, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Cops, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Crimson Avenger, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Demon, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Haywire, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Heroes against Hunger, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: History of the DC Universe, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Invasion, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Invasion: World without Heroes
    - Title from indicia: Legends, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Mask, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: 'Mazing Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: 'Mazing Man Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Nathaniel Dusk II, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Nathaniel Dusk Private Investigator II
    - Title from indicia: The New Titans, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Peacemaker, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Phantom Stranger, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Question, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Saga of Ra's Al Ghul, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Shadow of the Batman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Spiral Zone, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Suicide Squad, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 130: (Box 130)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Action Comics (Superman)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics No. 1, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of Superman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: DC Comics Presents, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Definitive Directory of the DC Universe, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Who's Who: The Definitive Directory of the DC Universe
    - Title from indicia: The Earth Stealers, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Superman: The Earth Stealers
    - Title from indicia: Hawkman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Hawkman Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Hex, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Lois Lane, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Man of Steel, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Oz-Wonderland Wars, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Slash Maraud, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Sonic Disruptors, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Superman Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Update '87, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Who's Who: The Definitive Director of the DC Universe Update '87
    - Title from indicia: Update '88, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Who's Who: The Definitive Director of the DC Universe Update '88
    - Title from indicia: World of Krypton, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: World of Metropolis, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: World of Smallville, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 131: (Box 131)
    - Title from indicia: Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, Issues from: 1980s
      - Cover Title: Advanced Dungeons & Dragons
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of the Outsiders, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Ambush Bug Stocking Stuffer, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Aquaman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Aquaman Special, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Captain Atom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Captain Atom Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Checkmate, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Cosmic Boy, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Cosmic Odyssey, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: DC Challenge, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Dragonlance, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Electric Warrior, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Flash Gordon, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Forever People, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The New Teen Titans, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The New Teen Titans Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Outcasts, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Outsiders, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Phantom, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Son of Ambush Bug, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 132: (Box 132)
    - Title from indicia: Blue Beetle, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Blue Devil, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Booster Gold, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Deadman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Gammarauders, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League International, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Justice League International Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Legend of Wonder Woman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: LEGION '89, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Legion of Super-Heroes Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Legionnaires Three, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Little Shop of Horrors, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Plastic Man, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: The Prisoner, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Super Powers, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Who's Who in the Legion of Super-Heroes, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wilddog, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman Annual, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Young All-Stars, Issues from: 1980s
    - Title from indicia: Young All-Stars Annual, Issues from: 1980s
  - Contents of Box 133: (Box 133)
    - Title from indicia: Detective Comics, Issues from: 1989-2000
      Issues 0, 601-750
  - Contents of Box 134: (Box 134)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Superman in Action Comics
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of Superman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Azrael: Agent of the Bat, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Batgirl, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Batman, Issues from: 2000s
      Issues 600-601
    - Title from indicia: Batman: Gotham Adventures, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: Gotham Knights, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: Legends of the Dark Knight, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Batman: Orpheus Rising, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Birds of Prey, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Catwoman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Dark Knight Strikes Again, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Deadman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Doom Patrol, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Flash, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Green Arrow, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Green Lantern, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Harley Quinn, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Haven: Broken City, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Hawkman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Impulse, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: JLA, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: JLA: Gatekeeper, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: JLA: Shogun of Steel, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Joker: Last Laugh, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Joker: Last Laugh Secret Files, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Joker: Last Laugh Secret Files and Origins
    - Title from indicia: JSA, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Just Imagine Stan Lee with Dave Gibbons Creating Green Lantern, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Just Imagine Stan Lee's Green Lantern
    - Title from indicia: Just Imagine Stan Lee with John Byrne Creating Robin, Issues from:2000s
      - Cover Title: Just Imagine Stan Lee's Robin
    - Title from indicia: Just Imagine Stan Lee... Secret Files and Origins, Issues from:2000s
      - Cover Title: Just Imagine Stan Lee's Secret Files and Origins
    - Title from indicia: Just Imagine Stan Lee with John Byrne Creating Shazam!, Issues from:2000s
      - Cover Title: Just Imagine Stan Lee's Shazam!
    - Title from indicia: Justice League Adventures, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Legion, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Nightwing, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Orion, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Power Company, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Robin, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Spectre, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Suicide Squad, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Supergirl, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Supergirl: Wings, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman Adventures, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman: The Man of Steel, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: The Titans, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Wonder Woman Secret Files and Origins, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Young Justice, Issues from: 2000s
  - Contents of Box 135: (Box 135)
    - Title from indicia: Action Comics, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
      - Cover Title: Superman in Action Comics
    - Title from indicia: Adventures of Superman, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Mann and Superman, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Millenium Edition: Superman No. 1, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superboy, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Supergirl, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman Adventures, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman and Batman: Generations II, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman and Batman: World's Funniest, Issues from: 2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman 80-page giant, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Superman, King of the World, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Superman: The Last God of Krypton, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Superman: The Man of Steel, Issues from: 1990s,2000s
    - Title from indicia: Superman: The Man of Tomorrow, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Superman: The Odyssey, Issues from:
    - Title from indicia: Superman: Our Worlds at War Secret Files, Issues from: 2000s
      - Cover Title: Superman: Our Worlds at War Secret Files and Origins